(Leonard:)Hey, Amy, what brings you
to our neck of the woods?
(Amy:)Your Neurology Department
Ioaned me a cuIture of prions...
(Amy:)...for my research
on bovine spongiform encephalopathy.
(Sheldon:)She popped by
to borrow a cup of mad cow disease.
(Amy:)It's hard to make degenerative brain
maladies hilarious, yet somehow you do.
(Howard:)That's fun to have in a lunchroom.
(Amy:)The real fun starts
when you pick the rat to feed it to...
(Amy:)...and maybe you choose the beady-eyed
mother who's been biting you all week.
(Howard:)Please, we're eating. Can we get that
off the table and change the subject?
(Sheldon:)Can we? Stand back...
(Sheldon:)...while I turn this conversation
into a "conver-sensation."
This time, it's your fauIt.
(Sheldon:)I have 100 alphabetized topics...
...from "Artichoke: Come on, people,
it's just a giant thistle"...
...to "Zzz:
The onomatopoetry of sleep."